jobnab.com 2015-05-22

# JobNab

**JobNab, Inc. (the "Company") takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.**

This policy describes the information collection, use, and dissemination practices of the Company and applies to the Company's collection, use, storage and disclosure of information by the Company on its Websites, including all its divisions, subsidiaries and related companies (collectively, the "Websites"), on various third party websites, and to the Company's other information collection. The Company is not responsible for the information collection or privacy practices of third party websites or applications. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that the Company does not own or control or to people that the Company does not employ or manage.

**Collection and Use of Your Information**

The Company collects personal information when you register with the Company, when you use the Company's products or services, when you visit the Company's pages or the pages of certain of the Company's partners. The Company may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.

When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, address, telephone numbers, employment history, education history, personal and professional references, including their names and email addresses. When you register with the Company and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

The Company automatically receives and records information from your computer and browser, including your IP address, cookie information, software and hardware attributes, and the page you request.

The aforementioned information is made available to the Company's clients, affiliates, advertisers, service providers, and other third parties that provide products or services for or through this website or for our business. The Company's clients affiliates, advertisers, service providers, and other third parties may also disclose such information to third parties they retain to provide products or services. If you have provided your contact information to us, we, and our past, current and future co-registration partners and affiliates, including but not limited to Amazon, Macy's, Zales, Crayola, Travelocity, Hanes, Fossil, Calvin Klein, Petsmart, One on One Marketing, LLC, Starbucks, Overstock.com, Clarins Paris, Big Dogs, Pac Sun, Little Tikes, Best Buy, Kodak, Zoobooks, The North Face, Buckle, Lane Bryant, Logitech, Sally Beauty Supply, William Rast, Blockbuster, may contact you for marketing purposes by telephone at the number you provided even if you are registered on any state or federal Do-Not-Call list.

We may use third parties to help operate our website and deliver products and services, and may share your personal information with our clients affiliates, advertisers, service providers, and other third parties (such as Website or database hosting companies, address list hosting companies, email service providers, analytics companies, distribution companies, fulfillment companies, and other similar service providers that use such information on our behalf). Unless otherwise stated, these companies do not have any right to use the personal information we provide to them beyond what is necessary for them to assist us. When you conduct e-commerce with one of the e-commerce affiliates or service providers to which the website may be linked, certain personal information such as your email and home address may be collected by the service provider's server and made available to us.

The Company only releases your information to third parties for the purposes listed above, except where permitted or required by law. The Company only utilizes your information for purposes authorized by you.

When you provide information regarding professional and personal references, the Company will contact your references and provide your references' information to the Company's clients who may contact your references consistent with their recruiting and hiring efforts.

**Cookies**

Some pages on this Website employ browser session "cookies." A cookie is a small piece of data that a Website transfers to your computer's hard disk to allow the server to distinguish your session from that of others while you are connected. Requests to send cookies are not designed to collect information about you, but only about your "browser session." The cookies make it easier for you to use the dynamic features of our Website. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by the Company and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Website security**

Security is a priority at the Company. Appropriate measures are taken to protect the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of information about our members, providers, employers, brokers, and anyone else that may want to use our Website.

Only authorized users are allowed to access the information. The Company enforces a high level of protection, i.e., 128-bit Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption, for securing transmissions between a user's browser and this Website. Content on this site is protected against unauthorized access.

**Email security**

Email sent over the Internet is not secure and should not be used to communicate confidential information to the Company. Please be aware that the Company cannot guarantee the confidentiality or security of any information you send to us over the Internet when using email. The Company shall not be liable for any breach of confidentiality resulting from such use of email via the Internet. The Company will not use email to communicate confidential information unless the email is secured in accordance with the Company Corporate Email Policy.

**Email Anti-Spam Policy:**

The Company does not send unsolicited commercial email through our systems. If you believe you have received an unsolicited commercial email from the Company on behalf of any of our advertisers, please send an email (with the reported unsolicited commercial email included or attached with the 'full header') to: [spamreport@jobnab.com](mailto:spamreport@jobnab.com).

**Unsubscribe Policy**

To unsubscribe from the Company's email lists, a person must send an email to [unsubscribe@jobnab.com](mailto:unsubscribe@jobnab.com). Our unsubscribe process impacts only the future delivery of electronic mailings disseminated by the Company on its own behalf. You may still receive electronic mailings sent on behalf of third parties and your personal information may still be shared with third parties for use in offline marketing and data appends, including email appends.

Unsubscribing from our electronic mailings will not automatically unsubscribe the information from third parties. Since third parties maintain separate databases from us you will need to unsubscribe from each source individually, if desired. This allows you the freedom to pick and choose which subscriptions to maintain and which to discontinue.

**Your California Privacy Rights**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our visitors who are California residents to request certain information regarding its disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to [privacy@jobnab.com](mailto:privacy@jobnab.com). In accordance with California Civil Code Sec. 1789.3, California resident users are entitled to know that they may file grievances and complaints with California Department of Consumer Affairs, 400 R Street, Suite 1080, Sacramento, CA 95814; or by phone at 916-445-1254 or 800-952-5210; or by email to [dca@dca.ca.gov](mailto:dca@dca.ca.gov).

**No Information Collected from Children.**

The Company will never knowingly collect any personal information about children under the age of 18. If we obtain actual knowledge that we have collected personal information about a child under the age of 18, that information will be immediately deleted from our database. Because it does not collect such information, the Company has no such information to use or to disclose to third parties. The Company has designed this policy in order to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA").

**Third Party Advertising**

Ads appearing on this Website may be delivered to users by the Company, or one of our Web advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad servers may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements they believe will be of most interest to you.

**Changes in Our Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy changes from time to time and changes are effective upon posting. Please check back frequently for updates as it is your sole responsibility to be aware of changes. We do not provide notices of changes in any manner other than by posting the changes at this Website.
